[Music]
I protect and
gain gur benefits drawbacks
welcome to holistic investment. in ICC
approve protect and gain plan or
nonparticipating linked individual
savings life insurance
plan reive
protect and gainp
prot and gain
inv f pfolio
unimited
freey portfolio
strategy 75 25
Equity oriented fund multicap growth
fundi income
fased pfolio
mank
07 135% per policy Administration Char
policy in the charge
0.34% of aned Premium
PR over a
perod premium payment frequency
married women protection
of
prium 80,000 policy term 40 years
premium paying term 10
years 3.58% 8% scenario final fund value
82.8
longm
and gation
pre-tax value post capital gain tax pox
value 2.54
prot andain final
Li longterm investment minimum policy
years
Prof finci help
inv next video